let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which social media platform came out in 2003?",
        answer: "Myspace",
        options: [
            "Myspace",
            "Twitter",
            "Facebook",
            "Tumblr"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which New York City building is the tallest:",
        answer: "One World Trade Center",
        options: [
            "Empire State Building",
            "Bank of America Tower",
            "One World Trade Center",
            "Statue of Liberty "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which U.S. president doesn’t/didn’t have a dog in the White House?",
        answer: "Trump",
        options: [
            "Trump",
            "Obama",
            "Bush",
            "Lincoln"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What does the “U” stand for in “UFO”?",
        answer: "Unidentified",
        options: [
            "Unidentified",
            "Under",
            "United",
            "Unique"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "After The Simpsons, what is the longest running TV show?",
        answer: "Law & Order",
        options:[
            "Law & Order",
            "Grey’s Anatomy",
            "Criminal Minds",
            "NCIS"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which one of these characters is not friends with Harry Potter? ",
        answer: "Draco Malfoy",
        options:[
            "Ron Weasley",
            "Neville Longbottom",
            "Draco Malfoy",
            "Hermione Granger"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Sodium bicarbonate is used in the kitchen as what?",
        answer: "baking soda",
        options:[
            "salt",
            "sugar",
            "baking soda",
            "vinegar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which two planets in our solar system are known as “ice giants”?",
        answer: "Neptune and Uranus",
        options:[
            "Neptune and Jupiter",
            "Uranus and Pluto",
            "Pluto and Jupiter",
            "Neptune and Uranus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Where in California is Disneyland located?",
        answer: "Los Angeles",
        options:[
            "Malibu",
            "Huntington Beach",
            "Los Angeles",
            "Anaheim"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The Da Vinci Code opens with a murder in which museum:",
        answer: "The Louvre",
        options:[
            "The Guggenheim",
            "The Louvre",
            "The Van Gogh museum",
            "The Metropolitan Museum of Art"
        ]
    },
    
]